I carry high my craven flag,
my ally I'm gonna fly and let my
struggles shoot me through the sky!
It'd be a pity if we
lingered here and let our
pretty sparks of life
blend aloud and disappear?
There may be fog that even
you can't navigate If someone
strong like you is lost then
who will set me straight?
Cause when the waves
cast, my heart exists?
It's been your kindness and your strength!
That would free me from the mist.
And just like that!
We move on.
Sail to a new dawn.
Weigh anchor, ride as high as you can!
I assure I don't need anger.
I go fast as I am, yeah.
I hear you laughing like
you're numb to it all?
Well, we're dashing together!
No, we're never gonna fall, you know!
The whole world may now be my enemy?
Water swirl, but I ain't backing
down so long as I'm free!
Thought I'll give it, come
round the current with me.
All in, wake up bright and
early, making for the peak we go!
I don't know.
Dark is the sky.
Fierce is the storm.
The wind blows.
At Onikachiwa.
Oh, the dragon roars.
The howling beasts sing feasting merrily.
Beneath the autumn leaves.
Dreams become reality.
At Habu Port.
The bold take to the sea.
The retainers of Kozuki Odin.
Returned at long last.
To battle they go.
A story of true loyalty.
So,
please allow me to
tell this tale modestly.
Our story begins on a dark,
stormy night not long ago.
One day before this year's Fire Festival.
Meanwhile, not far from
the flower capital,
Momonosuke and his friends
head toward Tokage Port?
hoping to catch Luffy before he sets sail.
So, you've changed your
mind about going to sea?
Uh-huh.
At least for now.
And I've already told Luffy about it.
You truly want to stay?
I'm surprised.
You want me gone?
Not at all.
On the contrary, it's
reassuring to have you.
But when we last spoke, you told me that
you had come to an important decision.
Well, Odin started his journey
by traveling across Wano.
I haven't even done that yet.
So I decided to follow his path properly.
I'll go out to see when the time is right.
That's fine, but I can't believe Luffy
discussed his departure with you.
Or more specifically, I can't believe
he failed to discuss it with me.
That traitor!
He's leaving without saying
goodbye to me and Kin'emon!
I don't understand!
What's your name?
Your father was a fool of a lord.
Tell me, who are you?
And why are you here? Oh, me?
Luffy, I'm gonna be king
of the pirates someday.
Cut the crap!
I don't care if you're a samurai!
I'm gonna be king of the
pirates someday! Ha! So what?
I shall be the Shogun of Wado someday!
and you'll be like a worm beneath my feet!
I'm not a worm or an eel!
Then you're a monkey, you saint!
What?
These are awesome!
What are you?
A figurehead, huh, Momo?
You just gonna cry?
I want to vanquish Emmerichino!
Hey, Momo.
Let's team up.
Moffey!
Hey, Momo!
It's okay, I know!
You're just a little crybaby
with a dumb top knot!
What are you gonna do anyway?
Nothing, and you know it too!
Gotta find a way to survive, okay?
Just hang on, and we'll come rescue you!
Because you're my friend!
Now, brat, one last time.
What is your name?
You want my name?
It's Kozuki Morinoste!
Hear me now!
I shall become the Shogun
of the Land of Plano!
So fly!
With your eyes open this time, I shall.
Your job is to stop Onigashima.
As for Kaido, I got this.
Hear that?
You're done for!
We've had our share of quarrels.
But does our adventure
together mean nothing to you?
There is a limit to how much
boorishness I can tolerate.
You're confusing personal
freedom with disrespect!
Right, Tinemon? Indeed.
Well spoken, my lord.
But if you don't mind, I must ask,
why do you run when you can fly?
Silence! Yes, sir.
I apologize for my insolence.
Now, Sir Luffy must answer
for disrespecting our Shogun.
If he cannot explain his vile actions
to us, we shall consider him an enemy.
Yes, that is the way of samurai!
Know that it is you who
trampled on our friendship,
Luffy, He saved the whole country.
Give him a break.
I will not.
He humiliated me.
I will strike him,
then fight him, and then make him pay
in whatever manner I deem most suitable.
Remember, we're enemies
the next time I see you.
Don't try to be friendly.
If you do, you might end up dead.
Okay, that's fine with me.
See you, Traffy!
Shut up.
I'll see you around, Jaggy.
I can't wait to kick your ass.
Time to set sail!
Your hope?
No, me!
Finally.
How dare you!
Stop right there!
Hi, guys!
We came here to send you off.
What were you thinking running
off without saying a word to us?
Kin'emon and I have known you for longer
than anyone else in Wano you scoundrel.
You have deeply offended the both of us.
You better have a good excuse.
Well, you're seeing me now.
Listen to me.
This is an order from the Shogun.
Okay.
Please don't go.
You make me so sad.
I want to stay with all of you. I don't...
I don't know what I'll do!
I don't think I can make it without you!
You're the reason I was able to live!
You gave me the strength to fight!
You all were the reason
I was able to smile again
Thank you for avenging
my father and mother
Thank you for saving my country
I am a fool So I struggle
to put this into words
But I fear what is to come
I need you here with me
He's not very Shogun-like He's
still a kid Give him a break
Usopp!
Right!
Ready to go! Incoming!
We were waiting on the Sunny
so we could give you this.
So don't Shoguns order me.
You got bigger, but I
know you're still a kid.
You're also a dumb little scaredy-cat.
And a crybaby.
But you know you're like
a little brother to me.
What is this your flag?
If things get tough we've
still got your back!
Fly that flag to send a message!
If bad guys see that it'll send a packet!
I promise you!
Messing with our friend means?
He's messing with us, and the Straw Hat
Pirates don't back down from a fight!
Your friend...
I'm one of you!
Kinema! Yamato!
Momo, if you guys want to become pirates,
we'll come and pick you up anytime,
but not if you're just going to cry.
Set sail!
Yama 2, stay tuned!
Of course! See ya!
Keep it super proud! We shall!
Make me proud out there, show god!
Good luck for my new stage!
Go easy on the crying
and you'll do just fine!
Remember to have fun, okay?
We'll meet again someday.
So take care until then!
I will grow stronger each day
till I surpass Kozuki Oden.
I know you'll make him proud.
Surpass me! Will you stop!
Okay, to Hakumai.
We're not leaving?
That's their official port.
They have a lift there to
lower our ship to sea level.
Oh, thank goodness.
I did not care for the waterfall.
My bones were quaking
just thinking about it.
Straw Hatch, where are
you and Trafalgar off to?
Are you going to use the
official port to leave water?
That sounds nice and peaceful.
It's a good choice for you.
Average pirates.
Don't blame you one bit.
You guys gotta stay safe, right?
Stay safe.
You amateurs.
Should take it easy.
Easy.
It's good to be safe.
Don't take the bait.
I don't like that look on your face.
Captain?
The official port is there for a reason.
Shut up and follow me.
To hell and back!
Switch sides!
You're an enabler, Beppo!
Chief Bay, let me take the helm!
No, don't listen to him!
Captain, please!
We are!
Lord Momonosuke's allies flew into
battle like gods of vengeance.
Tearing through lesser foes,
they reached to the sky where they
faced the Dragon King Kaido himself.
A monstrous Oiran stood beside him.
But even with her aid,
the dragon could not
withstand the winds of
change that blew at the
backs of our heroes.
But nearby, despite being burned,
Orochi had not met his end.
Brimming with contempt, he targeted our
princess Hiyori, who stood her ground.
Then whoosh!
Slash!
The vile serpent was felled
in one cut! But by who?
Why, Lord Odin's loyal retainer, Denjiro!
Odinji's final head was set ablaze!
The enemy of the Kozuki clan
paid for his treachery at last!
Thunder roared!
Kaido and Onigashima
itself were next to fall.
For twenty years, dark clouds
had covered the land of Wano,
blackening the entire realm.
But then, suddenly, the
clouds began to clear.
In the flower capital,
the festival carried on.
Its lively music floated
into the night sky.
But the snake lived, even
severed from its neck.
The head of Oruji glared with spite,
and from its mouth, a warning came.
The grudge of the Kurozumi clan will curse
the land of Wano for generations to come.
Your victory is but a force.
Princess Hiyori stood firm,
remembering the twenty years of
suffering her people had endured.
She returned the serpent's glare.
Lady Hiyori, stay away, cried Denjiro.
But she would not be deterred.
Our brave princess didn't flinch
in the face of the serpent's curse.
She delivered his obituary!
The fan in her hand bore the Kozuki crest.
She bit her lip and counted up the serpent
sins father mother brother i deliver this
verdict in the name of
all my people yeah the
best part you know the
words all together now
black charcoal is called Kurozumi
because it was born to burn
twilight songs ring out
in the city all night
crescent moon in reverse
at the port of rendezvous
now the tale is told
a victory for the brave in
gold revenge is had at last
the time for war and pain
has passed our
country is free
this is a story that will be
passed down for generations
of those who returned and
who returned peace to us
For today, that's all
that has been written.
But I'm certain that
this tale will continue.
And I will be certain to tell it.
So let us meet again!
Now where shall I fly this flag?
Thank you so much for watching.
The one who has cried again?
Just a little!
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go, look!
Don't forget to leave.
What will change?
The time is strong.
The time is there.
I will turn the light to see the light!
I will turn the light out.
Let's see the future.
We will be together.